okura-nikko.com 2016-08-09

# Privacy Policy - Okura Nikko Hotels

  * Basic Policy Concerning Information Security and the Protection of Personal Information of Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”).
  * Reservation Records Handling
  * Handling of One Harmony Membership Information
  * Handling of Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members Information
  * Handling of Other Information Registered on Website
  * Handling of Personal Information Other than Reservation Records, One Harmony Members, Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members, and Others registered on Website.
  * SSL
  * Use of Cookies

## Basic Policy Concerning Information Security and the Protection of Personal Information of Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”).

Given the importance of information security and the protection of personal information in the advanced information and communications society, ONHM shall endeavor to appropriately manage and protect information in its possession in accordance with the policy stated hereunder.

### 1\. Compliance with Laws and Regulations, etc.

ONHM shall comply with policies, guidelines, etc. prescribed in laws and regulations and by administrative organs.

### 2\. Establishment of a Management System

A management system shall be established within ONHM and the division of responsibilities shall be clarified.

### 3\. Compliance with Internal Policies, Rules, Guidelines, etc.

ONHM shall formulate and comply with internal policies, rules, guidelines, etc.

### 4\. Implementation of Safety Measures

ONHM shall implement safety measures, and take preventative measures against unauthorized access to information, and the loss, damage, falsification, leaks, etc. of information.

### 5\. Implementation of Training and Educational Activities

ONHM shall promote training and educational activities for employees with an aim to enhance their knowledge and awareness of information management so that information is managed appropriately through thorough familiarization with the said subject.

### 6\. Coordination with Subcontractors

If work relating to information management is subcontracted to other companies, then ONHM shall select a party with adequate experience and capabilities, shall prescribe matters concerning the duty of confidentiality in relevant agreements and shall ensure that information is managed appropriately.

### 7\. Operational Improvement Initiatives

ONHM shall regularly check whether information is being appropriately managed, and shall continuously exercise initiatives to improve operations.

### 8\. Measures Upon Occurrence of Accidents

If accidents occur, ONHM shall minimize damage and swiftly publish necessary information, and take appropriate measures, including measures to prevent recurrence thereof.

### 9\. Clarification of Inquiries Desk

ONHM shall establish an inquiry desk in order to respond swiftly in good faith, to inquiries, complaints and requests from customers.

### 10\. Publication of this Policy

ONHM shall widely publish policies concerning information security and the protection of personal information, including this Policy by posting it on its website, etc.

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015

## Reservation Records Handling

Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) shall handle reservation records as stated hereunder.

### 1\. Management of Personal Information

ONHM shall, with a recognition of the importance of customers’ personal information submitted by customers, strictly manage such information using computers, etc., paying close attention to the handling thereof.

### 2\. Shared Use

ONHM shall use the reservation records of customers in order to provide services closely related to travel such as hotel, air travel, etc., publicize products and campaigns, and conduct work associated thereto.

  1. Shared data items: customers’ name, telephone number, address, email address, age, gender, employer, etc., type of airline mileage program (aka FFP), FFP membership number, FFP tier, name of hotel at which the customer will stay, dates of stay, package plan, applicable rate, arrival time, specific requests, credit card number to guarantee reservations.
  2. Scope of Users: ONHM, member hotels of Okura Hotels & Resorts, Nikko Hotels International and Hotel JAL City chain operated by ONHM, group hotels in alliance with ONHM, Hotel Okura Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Group companies (*1), JAL Group Airlines (*2), and JAL Card Inc. 
    1. Hotel Okura Group companies are Hotel Okura Enterprise Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Space Solutions Co., Ltd. and Continental Foods Co., Ltd..
    2. JAL Group Airlines are Japan Airlines Co., Ltd., Japan Transocean Air Co., Ltd., J-AIR Co., Ltd., Japan Air Commuter Co., Ltd., Ryukyu Air Commuter Co., Ltd and Hokkaido Air System Co., Ltd.
  3. Administrator: ONHM

### 3\. Provision of Reservation Records to Travel Agents

ONHM shall provide the above information provided for in the above item 2 to travel agents if an inquiry is made based on a reservation number provided to the travel agent by a customer.

### 4\. Provision to Third Parties

Except for the abovementioned, ONHM shall not provide or disclose reservation records and information to third parties unless customers have given their consent or unless required in accordance with laws and regulations, etc.

### 5\. Confirming Reservations

ONHM shall issue a reservation confirmation concerning reservations accepted by the Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center following the finalization of a reservation by mail, fax or email, etc. to the address, telephone number, fax number or email address specified by customers. Furthermore, please note that when making reservations via our website, an email message confirming the reservation will be sent to the email address provided by the customer.

### 6\. Handling of Inquiries, etc.

ONHM shall accept inquiries, alterations, etc. relating to reservation records from customers as follows and shall respond in a swift and appropriate manner within reasonable bounds.

Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center  
(Toll free within Japan)  
0120-00-3741 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)  
0120-58-2586 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)

### 7\. Inquiries, etc. Relating to Other Reservations

Inquiries and alterations concerning reservation records from customers who have not made reservations with Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center should be made directly to the hotel, facility or travel agent, etc. that handled the reservation.

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015  
Revised on July 22, 2016

## Handling of One Harmony Membership Information

Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) shall handle the personal information of One Harmony (hereinafter referred to as “OHM”) Program Members as follows.

### 1\. Management of Personal Information

In operating the OHM system, with recognition of the importance of the personal information submitted by Members, ONHM shall treat such personal information with the utmost care, and safeguard such information under a strict computerized security system.

### 2\. Shared Use

ONHM may use the personal information submitted by members for the purpose of recording lodging history, inclusion in membership cards, issuance of membership cards, provision of hotel accommodations, food and beverage services and wedding services, provision of other services closely related to hotel usage, giving notices about promotional plans and questionnaires including those of the partner companies, product development, OHM program management, and all other activities related thereto.

  1. Shared Data Items: Membership number, name, date of birth, gender, address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address, place of employment (company name, department, title, address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address), types of membership cards, lodging history, reservation history, communication history, point records, types of airline mileage program (aka FFP), FFP membership number, FFP tier, preference for smoking or nonsmoking room, taste, memorial days such as wedding anniversary, etc.
  2. Scope of Data Users: ONHM, member hotels of Okura Hotels & Resorts, Nikko Hotels International and Hotel JAL City chain operated by ONHM, a part of group hotels in alliance with ONHM, a part of restaurants operated by Okura Enterprise Co., Ltd. or Continental Foods Co., Ltd., restaurants operated by Hotel Okura Tokyo Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Group companies (*1), JAL Group airline companies (*2), and JAL Card Inc. 
    1. Hotel Okura Group companies are Hotel Okura Enterprise Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Space Solutions Co., Ltd. and Continental Foods Co., Ltd..
    2. JAL Group Airlines are Japan Airlines Co., Ltd., Japan Transocean Air Co., Ltd., J-AIR Co., Ltd., Japan Air Commuter Co., Ltd. and Ryukyu Air Commuter Co., Ltd.,Hokkaido Air System Co., Ltd.
  3. Administrator : ONHM

### 3\. Provision of personal information to third parties

ONHM shall not provide Member’s personal information to any third party except when there is the prior consent of a Member or a prescription in the Terms and Conditions herein and related rules and regulations, or it is required pursuant to applicable laws.

### 4\. Inquiries

Members’ requests for changes to or deletions of their own registered personal information or other inquiries shall be dealt with in a swift and appropriate manner within reasonable bounds upon personal enquiry by a Member.

OHM Office  
0120-80-3789 (Toll free within Japan) or +81-(0)3-3224-6617  
(9:30 – 18:00JST, Monday through Friday excluding national holidays, and year-end and New Year holiday period)

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015  
Revised on July 22, 2016 

## Handling of Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members Information

Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) shall handle personal information on Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members in the following manner.  
* Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members refer to those who have registered special IDs with ONHM exclusively used for online reservations.

### 1\. Management of Personal Information

ONHM shall, with a recognition of the importance of personal information submitted by members, strictly manage such information using computers, paying close attention to the handling thereof.

### 2\. Shared Use

ONHM shall jointly use personal information provided by members in order to provide hotel services and services closely related to hotels, provide advertising and promotional materials and questionnaires including those relating to affiliated companies, conduct product development, and for any other work associated thereto.

  1. Shared data items: name, date of birth, gender, address, telephone number, email address, profession, employer (company, department, address, and telephone number), type of airline mileage program (aka FFP), FFP membership number, FFP tier, tier of membership, membership number, reservation history, lodging history, etc.
  2. Scope of Users: ONHM, member hotels of Okura Hotels & Resorts, Nikko Hotels International and Hotel JAL City chain operated by ONHM, group hotels in alliance with ONHM, Hotel Okura Co., Ltd. and Hotel Okura Group Companies(*1). 
    1. Hotel Okura Group companies are Hotel Okura Enterprise Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Space Solutions Co., Ltd. and Continental Foods Co., Ltd..
  3. Administrator: ONHM

### 3\. Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties

Except for the abovementioned, ONHM shall not provide or disclose personal information to third parties unless members have given their consent in advance, or disclosure is required in accordance with laws and regulations, etc.

### 4\. Inquiries, etc. Relating to Personal Information

If a member contacts the inquiry desk with an inquiry or request to alter or suspend the use of their personal information, such inquiry shall be dealt with in a swift and appropriate manner within reasonable bounds. In addition, the inquiry desk shall accept feedback relating to the handling of personal information.

Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center  
(Toll free within Japan)  
0120-00-3741 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)  
0120-58-2586 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015

## Handling of Other Information Registered on Website

Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) shall handle personal information such as responses to online questionnaires, application to various events to include prizes, request for information materials, etc. inserted or registered by customers on website in the following manners.

### 1\. Management of Personal Information

ONHM shall, with a recognition of the importance of personal information, strictly manage such information using computers, paying close attention to the handling thereof.

### 2\. Disclosure, Revision, and Suspension of Use of Personal Information

Any request for reference, changes or suspension of use of personal information is accepted here.

Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center  
(Toll free within Japan)  
0120-00-3741 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)  
0120-58-2586 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)

### 3\. Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties

ONHM shall not provide or disclose personal information to third parties unless members have given their consent in advance, or disclosure is required in accordance with laws and regulations, etc.

### 4\. Personal Information in Linked External Websites

ONHM shall assume no management responsibility whatsoever for the gathering of personal information conducted by other companies’ websites introduced on ONHM website.

### 5\. Data Protection

ONHM website uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology as a safety measure on all pages in which personal information is inserted when gathering customers’ personal information. As a result, it encrypts the data traveling across the Internet and prevents data leaks.

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015

## Handling of Personal Information Other than Reservation Records, One Harmony Members, Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members, and Others registered on Website.

In addition to personal information in reservation records, personal information of One Harmony members, Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members, and others registered on website, Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) shall handle such personal information as received directly from customers or obtained from travel agents and companies which have contractual relations with ONHM in the following manners.

### 1\. Management of Personal Information

ONHM shall, with a recognition of the importance of customers’ personal information submitted by customers, strictly manage such information using computers, etc., paying close attention to the handling thereof.

### 2\. Purpose of Use of Personal Information

Personal information provided shall be used within the scope necessary to achieve the following purposes.

  1. To provide appropriate services to satisfy preference and request of customers, based on past usage information at ONHM, member hotels of Okura Hotels & Resorts, Nikko Hotels International and Hotel JAL City chain operated by ONHM (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM Member Hotels”).
  2. To provide details regarding ONHM Member Hotels, group hotels in alliance with ONHM (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM Alliance Hotels”).
  3. To provide details regarding accommodations, wedding services, food and beverage services, health club services, original products, and cultural projects of ONHM Member Hotels and ONHM Alliance Hotels.
  4. To analyze responses to questionnaires to improve services and for marketing purposes at ONHM Member Hotels and ONHM Alliance Hotels.
  5. To conduct marketing activities for ONHM.
  6. If customers have agreed in cases other than the above, and when ONHM, ONHM Member Hotels, and ONHM Alliance Hotels deem it necessary to contact customers.

### 3\. Inquiries, etc. Relating to Personal Information

If a customer contacts the inquiry desk with an inquiry or request to alter or suspend the use of their personal information, such inquiry shall be dealt with in a swift and appropriate manner within reasonable bounds. In addition, the inquiry desk shall accept feedback relating to the handling of personal information.

Okura Nikko Hotels Reservation Center  
(Toll free within Japan)  
0120-00-3741 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)  
0120-58-2586 (9:30 – 18:00JST, excluding year-end and New Year holiday period)

### 4\. Provision of Personal Information to third Parties

Personal information shall not be provided or disclosed to third parties except when falling under any of the following cases.

  1. To be shared by ONHM Member Hotels, ONHM Alliance Hotels, Hotel Okura Co., Ltd., and Hotel OkuraGroup Companies(*1).
  2. To be shared with contractors who have entered into agreements that prohibit use of personal information for any purposes other than the specific work outsourced by ONHM.
  3. When customers have given consent in advance.
  4. When required in accordance with laws and regulations. 
    1. Hotel Okura Group companies are Hotel Okura Enterprise Co., Ltd., Hotel Okura Space Solutions Co., Ltd. and Continental Foods Co., Ltd..

Revised on October 1st, 2015

## SSL

SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) refers to the protocol for encrypting and transmitting information over the internet. SSL is a security function that aims to protect important information such as personal information transferred over the Internet from theft, falsification and spoofing by third parties. On the website operated by Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) the accommodation reservation page for inserting personal information is an SSL secure page. (Certain pages allow users to select non-SSL communication.)

### 1\. Importance of SSL

The encryption of protocols currently used on the internet is not regulated and thus third parties are able to insert line monitors, PCs, etc. into lines to view information that crisscrosses the internet. The Internet is a network made up of interconnecting websites and a number of relay sites exist between access points and users, making it difficult to grasp whether a site is safe. For this reason, ONHM website prevents eavesdropping, etc. by third parties by utilizing secure communication using SSL when transmitting important information, especially personal information, etc. over the Internet.

### 2.SSL Structure

SSL first conducts electronic authentication between ONHM and customers prior to customers’ sending personal information (digital certificates and digital signatures), and transmits data after conducting cross certification. In doing so, exchanges between ONHM and customers are disturbed by random digits, and false transmissions to third parties posing as customers who attempt to steal data are prevented. Furthermore, information transmitted using SSL is encrypted using a method which combines two types of encryption methods; public key encryption (RSA) and symmetric key encryption (private key cryptography). An electronic “key” is required to decipher this information. Even if information is intercepted by third parties, it is impossible to decrypt encrypted information without the correct key. Although the number of available keys is finite, it is extremely difficult for third parties to decrypt information as it requires an unrealistically long time, even if work is conducted computationally using a computer, etc., to find the right key by testing all keys in turn.

### 3\. SSL Enabled Browsers

A special configuration is not necessary in order to use SSL. SSL functions automatically when using SSL enabled browsers such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc. in their default configuration. It may not be possible to access SSL secure pages or enter information when using browsers that do not support SSL.

* It may not be possible to transmit information using SSL due to FireWall configurations if the customer is connected to the internet via a FireWall on an internal LAN such as a LAN within a company.

### 4\. Data Protection

The website operated by ONHM uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology on the Okura Nikko Hotels Web Members’ page, the credit card payment page and other pages in which personal information is inserted as a safety measure when gathering customers’ personal information. As a result, it encrypts data traveling across the internet and prevents data leaks.

This document is posted only for the purpose of providing information to customers. It does not intend to recommend, request, or demand the use or otherwise of any specific software products.

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015

## Use of Cookies

Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “ONHM”) may send information called cookies to customers’ computers in order to improve user-friendliness for customers.

Customers may change their browser’s settings so as to reject cookies or to display warning messages when accepting cookies. Virtually all ONHM website services can be used without browsers accepting cookies, however, please note that certain services cannot be used without cookies when making accommodation reservations.

Revised on April 1st, 2013  
Revised on October 1st, 2015

## Privacy Policy Revisions

Significant modifications to this Policy shall be announced on this website. Please check the website on a constant basis for up-to-date information on other minor modifications. Please note that Okura Nikko Hotel Management Co., Ltd. shall assume no responsibility whatsoever for trouble resulting from failure to make such checks.
